Kyros, we are so disappointed. How could you? Didn’t we ask you to stay out of it? Didn’t we tell you that your pride will be the end of you?
Look where your recklessness got you.
My recklessness? Really?!
Amos, you are the wisest of us. You were the one I came to and asked to use the power of creators against the enemies who were tearing our allod apart.
Listen to yourself, Kyros!
This power was granted to us so we could create, not destroy!
It was meant to be. And it was fate that sent immortal warriors to help us. Those who do not fear death. If you waited...
Immortality is a poison that eats away at your souls!
Look at yourself! You’re trembling! Shaking at the thought that your existence might end one day.
And I’d give anything to go back and die in her place there... but I can’t.
This is madness...! We are all grieving for Aellona. But trembling? Shaking?
We do not fear death, but we do not invite it upon ourselves either, unlike you.
You are not thinking clearly, Kyros. Aellona’s blood is on your hands, and I am forced to...
Quiet!
Blood on my hands... You’re right, my friend.
I didn’t know why the creators made me like this - all I bring is death.
I didn’t... until this morning. But now I know what my purpose is!
I’ll take the blame for this blood and I’ll destroy this false immortality.
Don’t even try to stop me!